ANTHONY PFAFF

SKILLS

I have earned a lot of experience working in team settings and remaining calm in stressful situations to perform to the best of my abilities. Due to my experience working in a restaurant and speaking to customers daily, I have no problem talking to strangers and creating a welcoming atmosphere for everyone around me.

EXPERIENCE

Jumbo & Delicious, Hendersonville TN - Assistant Manager

August 2021 - August 2024

- Family-owned restaurant run by Viola Albert and her family
- Spent lots of time working on a team with other cooks to make quality food on time
- Learned how to remain calm during stressful situations
- Gained experience speaking with customers and maintaining a welcoming atmosphere within the restaurant

MHMS Team 1030 Robotics - Co-President

June 2023 - December 2023

- Merrol Hyde Magnet School Robotics team sponsored by Scott Horton
- Gained experience in mechatronics by building a robot from scratch to perform medical-themed tasks
- Used critical thinking skills and the scientific method to come up with efficient solutions to complex problems
- Invested a large portion of my time into perfecting my robot-driving and communication skills to ensure that my teammates and I could perform to the best of our abilities

Hope City Church, Gallatin TN - Launch Team

June 2023 - PRESENT

- Helped to found a new church dedicated to sharing the hope of the gospel
- Collaborated with a group of friends and family to deliver church services to the people of Gallatin TN
- Created and mastered an efficient system of setting up and tearing down the services every week

EDUCATION

Merrol Hyde Magnet School – High School Diploma

August 2020 - May 2024

- 3.96 GPA
- National Honors Society Member
- Co-President of the Robotics Team

AWARDS + ACHIEVENENTS

- AP Scholar (2023)
- AP Scholar with Distinction (2024)
- 1st Place Music City BEST Robotics Competition at Lipscomb University (2023)
- 32 ACT (Composite)
- CUM LAUDE Certification on the National Latin Exam